Guide to the Black Sport in Pittsburgh Oral History Collection ca.1980 AIS.1987.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Rob Ruck Collection of Black Sport
1979-1994, bulk 1989-1994
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Ruck, Rob
AIS.1987.01
15 Linear Feet (91 Cassettes; 30 Transcripts/Notes)
Dr. Rob Ruck is a well-known author and historian of the history of sport and the role it plays in today's society. Ruck has authored numerous books on the subject as well as producing documentary films. The bulk of the collection consist of research material and footage used in the documentary Kings of the Hill: Baseballs Forgotten Men focusing on the history of Negro League Baseball in the city of Pittsburgh. The collection includes various audiovisual production elements containing visual footage and interviews with prominent individuals in the Pittsburgh Black community and former Negro League Baseball players. Of particular interest are the 54 interviews of individuals involved in Black baseball clubs in and around Pittsburgh. The interviews were conducted in the early 1980's by Rob Ruck, then a graduate student in the Department of History, University of Pittsburgh and formed the foundation for his book, Sandlot Seasons: sport in Black Pittsburgh published in 1987 by the University of Illinois Press.
Scope and Content Notes
The Rob Ruck Collection of Black Sport consists of research material documenting the history of Negro League Baseball in Pittsburgh for use in the documentary, Kings of the Hill: Baseballs Forgotten Men. The material includes photographic prints of various Negro League players and teams. Of particular interest are the 54 interviews of individuals involved in Black baseball clubs in and around Pittsburgh. The interviews were conducted in the early 1980's by Rob Ruck, then a graduate student in the Department of History, University of Pittsburgh and formed the foundation for his book, Sandlot Seasons: sport in Black Pittsburgh published in 1987 by the University of Illinois Press. Interviews of note include Charles "Teenie" Harris, Monte Irvin, Harold Tinker, Mal Goode, August Wilson, Bob Thurman and others. The collection also includes an assortment of video and audio needed for the film's production including B-roll, photographs, rough cuts, music, and sound effects, and printed ephemera. Along with research material on Negro League Baseball, the collection consists of material focused on baseball in Latin America. This materal includes original photographs taken by Dr. Ruck throughout the Carribean and South America in countries the Dominican Repulic, Cuba, Venezuela and Nicaragua.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Rob Ruck, February 1987 and November 2023.
Previous Citation
Black Sport in Pittsburgh Records of the Oral History Collection, ca.1980, AIS.1987.01, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Black Sport in Pittsburgh, OH 87:1, Archives of Industrial Society, Hillman Library, University of Pittsburgh.
Sports -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Athletes -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh -- Interviews; Interviews -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Oral histories (Literary genre); Oral history; Sports; Interviews; African American athletes -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh -- Interviews; African Americans -- Sports; African Americans -- Interviews; Ethnic groups
- Audio and Visual Material, no date; I.
  - Visual Material, no date
    - Negro Baseball Dubs; Tapes 0, 1, 2; Teenie Harris, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 1, Cassette 1)
    - Negro Baseball Dubs; Tapes 3, 4, 5; Harold Tinker, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 1, Cassette 2)
    - Negro Baseball Dubs; Tapes 6, 7, 8; Harold Tinker, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 1, Cassette 3)
    - Negro Baseball Dubs; Tapes 9, 10, 11; Harold Tinker, John Holway, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 1, Cassette 4)
    - Negro Baseball Dubs; Tapes 12, 13, 14; John Holway, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 1, Cassette 5)
    - Negro Baseball Dubs; Tapes 15, 16, 17; John Holway, Monte Irvin, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 1, Cassette 6)
    - Negro Baseball Dubs; Tapes 18, 19, 20; Monte Irvin, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 1, Cassette 7)
    - Negro Baseball Dubs; Tapes 21, 22, 23; Monte Irvin, Bob Thurman, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 1, Cassette 8)
    - Negro Baseball Dubs; Tapes 25, 26, 27; Bob Thurman, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 1, Cassette 9)
    - Negro Baseball Dubs; Tapes 28, 29, 30; Bob Thurman, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 1, Cassette 10)
    - Negro Baseball Dubs, Tapes 31, 32; Jake Milliones, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 1, Cassette 11)
    - Negro Baseball Dubs; Tapes 33, 34; Norris Coleman, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 1, Cassette 12)
    - Kings On The Hill Photo Reel 1, 2, 3, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 2, Cassette 1)
    - Kings On The Hill Photo Reel 4, 5, 6, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 2, Cassette 2)
    - Kings On The Hill Photo Reel beta 7, 8, 9, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 2, Cassette 3)
    - Kings On The Hill Photo Reel 10, 11, 12, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 2, Cassette 4)
    - Kings On The Hill Photo Reel, Tapes 13, 14, 15, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 2, Cassette 5)
    - Kings On The Hill Photo Reel 15, 16, January 31, 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 2, Cassette 6)
    - Kings On The Hill Photo Reel 17, 18, January 31, 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 2, Cassette 7)
    - Kings On The Hill Photo Reel 16, 17, 18, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 2, Cassette 8)
    - Kings Photo Reel 1, Dubs of Beta's 19, 20, 21, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 2, Cassette 9)
    - King Photo Reel 2, Dub of 21 Continued, 22, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 2, Cassette 10)
    - Kings On The Hill Photos, March 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 2, Cassette 11)
    - Kings On The Hill Photos (Re-Shoot), November 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 2, Cassette 12)
    - Trouppe Footage, Reel 1, Part 1 of 2, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 3, Cassette 1)
    - Trouppe Footage, Reel 2, Part 2 of 2, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 3, Cassette 2)
    - Troupe Footage, Kings On the Hill WTAE Steel mills, Negro Leaders Reunion, no date; VHS (Box 3, Cassette 3)
    - Troupe Footage, Kings On the Hill WTAE Steel mills, Negro Leaders Reunion, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 3, Cassette 4)
    - Baseball Newsreel 35 Minute, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 3, Cassette 5)
    - Dub of Teenie Footage + Open Cut 8, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 3, Cassette 6)
    - Wylie Avenue Days, August 30, 1991; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 3, Cassette 7)
    - Kings On The Hill Major League Footage, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 3, Cassette 8)
    - Kings On The Hill Footage, Major League Baseball, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 3, Cassette 9)
    - Kings On The Hill Footage, Master, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 3, Cassette 10)
    - Satchel Paige Last Game, Master for Kings On The Hill, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 3, Cassette 11)
    - Dub Satchel Last Game, 2 Cuts Clemente, New Opening Kings, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 3, Cassette 12)
    - Kings On The Hill Master Reel #1, November 16, 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 3, Cassette 13)
    - Kings On The Hill Master Cassette 2, November 16, 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 3, Cassette 14)
    - Mal Goode; Tapes 11, 12, 13, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 4, Cassette 1)
    - Mal Goode; Tapes 14, 15, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 4, Cassette 2)
    - Mal Goode, August Wilson; Tapes 18, 19, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 4, Cassette 3)
    - August Wilson; Tapes 18, 19, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 4, Cassette 4)
    - John Wideman; Tapes 20, 21, 22, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 4, Cassette 5)
    - Odile Striblin; Tapes 23, 24, 25, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 4, Cassette 6)
    - Odile Striblin, Clarence Bruce; Tapes 26, 1, 2, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 4, Cassette 7)
    - Kings On the Hill, Joe Black, Reel 1, February 26, 1993; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 4, Cassette 8)
    - Kings On the Hill, Joe Black, Reel 2, February 26, 1993; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 4, Cassette 9)
    - Kings On the Hill, Joe Black, Reel 1, February 26, 1993; Betacam SP (Box 4, Cassette 10)
    - Kings On the Hill, Joe Black, Reel 2, February 26, 1993; Betacam SP (Box 4, Cassette 11)
    - Dennis Morgan, August 31, 1990; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 4, Cassette 12)
    - Kings On the Hill, Opening With Joe Black, March 3, 1993; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 4, Cassette 13)
    - Kings On the Hill, Buck Leonard Interview, Tapes 1 and 2, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 4, Cassette 14)
    - Kings On the Hill, Buck Leonard Interview, Tapes 3 and 4, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 4, Cassette 15)
    - Kings On The Hill: Baseball's Forgotten Men, Stereo, October 2, 1993; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 1)
    - Kings On The Hill: Baseball's Forgotten Men, October 2, 1993; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 2)
    - Kings On The Hill: Baseball's Forgotten Men (For Preview Only), Use for Dub Master, April 28, 1993; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 3)
    - Kings On The Hill, September 22, 1999; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 4)
    - Edit Kings, Cued to Re-ordering of Josh Sequence, July 10, 1995; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 5)
    - 1994 Robert M. Bennett Award, Kings On The Hill: Baseball's Forgotten Men, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 6)
    - Kings On The Hill: Baseball's Forgotten Men, Rough Cut IV, Tracked For Editing, Working Script, February 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 7)
    - Kings On The Hill Complete Show, December 15, 1993; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 8)
    - Kings On The Hill, Master, Tracked for Editing, Cut 5, March 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 9)
    - Kings On The Hill, Master, Blacked for Editing, Cut 6, June 22, 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 10)
    - Kings On The Hill, Master, Blacked for Editing, Cut 7, July 9, 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 11)
    - Kings On The Hill Insert Master, 5 Cuts, September 10, 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 12)
    - Kings On The Hill, Dub Cut 5, April 10, 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 13)
    - Kings On The Hill, Rough Cut 2, October 4, 1991; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 5, Cassette 14)
    - Negro Leagues #101, Kings On The Hill Photo Layoff, no date; Betacam SP (Box 6, Cassette 1)
    - Negro Leagues #102, Kings On The Hill Photo Layoff, no date; Betacam SP (Box 6, Cassette 2)
    - Negro Leagues #103, Photo Layoff Reel 3, no date; Betacam (Box 6, Cassette 3)
    - Negro Leagues #104, Negro League Project, no date; Betacam (Box 6, Cassette 4)
    - Negro Leagues #110, Music Layover, no date; Betacam (Box 6, Cassette 5)
    - Negro League Baseball (Preview), no date; VHS (Box 6, Cassette 6)
    - Negro League Archive Film, KDKA TV, Master, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 6, Cassette 7)
    - Negro Leagues: Demo Stills, Unedited From Beta, Dub of Beta #103, February 1991; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 6, Cassette 8)
    - Negro Leagues: Demo Stills, Unedited (from Beta), no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 6, Cassette 9)
    - National Archives, Negro Leagues, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 6, Cassette 10)
    - Negro League Archive Film, KDKA TV, no date; VHS (Box 6, Cassette 11)
    - Negro Leagues Reunion, no date; VHS (Box 6, Cassette 12)
    - Kings On The Hill: Baseball's Forgotten Men, Rough Cut, September 1992; VHS (Box 8, Cassette 7)
    - Kings On The Hill: Baseball's Forgotten Men, Rough Cut V, no date; VHS (Box 8, Cassette 8)
    - Kings On The Hill: Baseball's Forgotten Men, Rough Cut 2, no date; VHS (Box 8, Cassette 9)
    - Kings On The Hill Cut 3, no date; VHS (Box 8, Cassette 10)
    - "Kings On The Hill" Showcase Presentation, no date; VHS (Box 8, Cassette 11)
    - "Kings On The Hill" Showcase Presentation, no date; VHS (Box 8, Cassette 12)
    - "Kings On The Hill" Showcase Presentation, no date; VHS (Box 8, Cassette 13)
    - "Kings On The Hill" Showcase Presentation, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 8, Cassette 14)
    - Kings On The Hill: The Story of the Negro Leagues, Showcase Presentation, no date; VHS (Box 8, Cassette 15)
    - Kings On The Hill: Baseball's Forgotten Men, San Pedro Productions, Ltd, no date; VHS (Box 8, Cassette 16)
    - Kings On The Hill: Baseball's Forgotten Men, San Pedro Productions, Ltd, no date; VHS (Box 8, Cassette 17)
    - Kings On The Hill, Tape 1, no date; VHS (Box 8, Cassette 18)
    - Kings On The Hill Photos, Reel 1, June 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 8, Cassette 19)
    - Kings On The Hill Photos, Reel 2, June 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 8, Cassette 20)
    - Kings Photo Tape 1, Time Code 2:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 1)
    - Kings Photo Tape 2, Time Code 2:20:00-2:40:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 2)
    - Kings Photo Tape 3, Time Code 2:41:00-3:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 3)
    - Kings Photo Tape 4, Time Code 3:00:00-3:20:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 4)
    - Kings Photo Tape 5, Time Code 3:20:00-3:40:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 5)
    - Kings Photo Tape 6, Time Code 3:40:00-4:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 6)
    - Kings Photo Tape 7, Time Code 4:00:00-4:20:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 7)
    - Kings Photo Tape 8, Time Code 4:21:00-4:40:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 8)
    - Kings Photo Tape 9, Time Code 4:42:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 9)
    - Kings Photo Tape 10, Time Code 5:03:00-5:21:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 10)
    - Kings Photo Tape 11, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 11)
    - Kings Photo Tape 12, Time Code 5:40:00-5:60:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 12)
    - Kings Photo Tape 13, Time Code 7:00:00-7:20:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 13)
    - Kings Photo Tape 14, Time Code 8:00:00-9:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 14)
    - Kings Photo Tape 15, Time Code 9:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 15)
    - Kings Photo Tape 16, Time Code 10:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 16)
    - Kings Photo Tape 17, Time Code 10:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 17)
    - Kings Photo Tape 18, Time Code 10:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 18)
    - Kings Photo Tape 19, Time Code 19:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 19)
    - Kings Photo Tape 20, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 20)
    - Kings Photo Tape 21, Time Code 21:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 21)
    - Kings Photo Tape 22, Time Code 22:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 22)
    - Kings Photo Tape 15, Time Code 15:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 23)
    - Kings Photo Tape 16, Time Code 16:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 24)
    - Kings Photo Tape 17, Time Code 17:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 25)
    - Kings Photo Tape 18, Time Code 18:00:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 26)
    - Kings Photo Tape 1, Time Code 1:00:00-1:20:00, March 27, 1992; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 27)
    - Kings Photo Tape 2, Time Code 1:20:00-1:40:00, March 27, 1992; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 28)
    - Kings Photo Tape 3, Time Code 1:40:00-1:60:00, March 27, 1992; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 29)
    - Kings Photo Tape 4, Time Code 2:00:00-2:05:00, March 27, 1992; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 30)
    - Kings Photo Tape 1, Time Code 3:00:00, November 1992; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 31)
    - Kings Photos Tape 2, Time Code 4:00:00, November 1992; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 32)
    - Kings Photos, Time Code 1:00:00-1:21:00, June 19, 1992; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 33)
    - Kings Photos, Time Code 1:21:00-1:39:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 34)
    - Kings Photos, Time Code 1:40:00-1:59:00, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 35)
    - Kings Photos, Time Code 2:00:00-2:21:00, Master, no date; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 36)
    - Kings On The Hill Stills, Reel 1 of 2, March 17, 1993; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 37)
    - Kings On The Hill Stills, Reel 2 of 2, March 17, 1993; Betacam (Box 9, Cassette 38)
    - Kings Photos Reels 7-12, no date; VHS (Box 9, Cassette 39)
    - Kings On The Hill, Ossie Davis Narration, Reel One, Master Dub, July 9, 1993; 1 inch Film Reel (Box 10, Reel 1)
    - Kings On The Hill, Ossie Davis Narration, Reel Two, Master Dub, July 9, 1993; 1 inch Film Reel (Box 10, Reel 2)
    - Kings On The Hill, Dub Reel, Various Bump Ups, including credits, Background, Promo, March 29, 1993; 1 inch Film Reel (Box 10, Reel 3)
    - Kings On The Hill, Stereo Music Submaster, No video, March 29, 1993; 1 inch Film Reel (Box 10, Reel 4)
    - Kings On The Hill, Mixed Master, April 27, 1993; 1 inch Film Reel (Box 10, Reel 5)
    - Kings On The Hill, Promo Voice-over, no date; 1/4 inch Film Reel (Box 17, Reel 1)
    - Voice-over Ossie Davis, no date; 1/4 inch Film Reel (Box 17, Reel 2)
    - "Kings On The Hill" Showcase Presentation, no date; 1 inch Film Reel (Box 17, Reel 3)
    - Kings On The Hill, Tails Out, Reel 1, no date; 1/2 inch Film Reel (Box 17, Reel 4)
    - Kings On The Hill, Tails Out, Reel 2, no date; 1/2 inch Film Reel (Box 17, Reel 5)
    - Kings On The Hill: Baseball Forgotten Men, Reel 1, no date; 3 1735 073 034 427; 16 mm Film Reel
    - Kings On The Hill: Baseball Forgotten Men, Reel 2, no date; 3 1735 073 034 435; 16 mm Film Reel
    - Cuba, Straight, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 12, Cassette 1)
    - Cuba, TBC-2, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 12, Cassette 2)
    - Dominican Republic Tape 5, no date; Betacam SP (Box 12, Cassette 3)
    - Dominican Republic Tape 6, no date; Betacam SP (Box 12, Cassette 4)
    - Dominican Republic Tape 7, no date; Betacam SP (Box 12, Cassette 5)
    - Dominican Republic Tape 8, no date; Betacam SP (Box 12, Cassette 6)
    - Dominican Republic Tape 9, no date; Betacam SP (Box 12, Cassette 7)
    - Trujillo and Sports Cavalcade, Submaster, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 12, Cassette 8)
    - Trujillo and Sports Cavalcade, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 12, Cassette 9)
    - Trujillo, 1937, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 12, Cassette 10)
    - 1953 Caribbean Series, no date; VHS (Box 12, Cassette 11)
    - 1953 Caribbean Series, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 12, Cassette 12)
    - Japanese Footage, Tapes 3, 4, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 13, Cassette 1)
    - Murrin/ Bourne, Tapes 5,6, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 13, Cassette 2)
    - Japanese Footage, Tapes 7,8, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 13, Cassette 3)
    - Only The Ball Was White, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 13, Cassette 4)
    - Only The Ball Was White, no date; VHS (Box 13, Cassette 5)
    - Roughcut Jackie Stealing Home, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 13, Cassette 6)
    - Work tape, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 13, Cassette 7)
    - "The History of Great Black Baseball Players", American Sports Heroes, 1990; VHS (Box 13, Cassette 8)
    - Figuras Del Deporte, Rob Ruck, January 16, 1988; VHS (Box 13, Cassette 9)
    - "There was Always Sun Shining Someplace: Life in the Negro Baseball Leagues", 1984; VHS (Box 13, Cassette 10)
    - Vibrations (Sandlot Seasons), Rob Ruck, no date; VHS (Box 13, Cassette 11)
    - PBS Baseball, Music Layoff, Final Shots, Work Tape, no date; Betacam (Box 13, Cassette 12)
    - August Wilson WQED Pittsburgh Production, no date; VHS (Box 13, Cassette 13)
    - Ernie Kovacs A and E Biography Documentary, no date; VHS (Box 13, Cassette 14)
    - The Bingo Long Traveling All-Stars & Motor Kings, no date; VHS (Box 13, Cassette 15)
    - "A League Second To None", JMC Productions, November 12, 1994; VHS (Box 13, Cassette 16)
    - Forbes Field, no date; DVD (Box 13, Disc 17)
  - Audio Material, no date
    - Kings Music, Honky Tonk, Erroll Garner, September 22, 1992; Betacam SP (Box 7, Cassette 1)
    - Kings Sound Effects, Dub of Beta, no date; Betacam SP (Box 7, Cassette 2)
    - Kings On The Hill Sound Effects, Master, no date; Betacam SP (Box 7, Cassette 3)
    - Kings Sound Effects, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 7, Cassette 4)
    - Kings Music Reel 9, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 7, Cassette 5)
    - Kings On The Hill Music Transfer, Stereo, September 11, 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 7, Cassette 6)
    - Kings On The Hill Music, Honky Tonk, Erroll Garner, September 22, 1992; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 7, Cassette 7)
    - Kings Music Reel 9, Betacam SP (Box 7, Cassette 8)
    - Kings On The Hill Music Transfer, Stereo, Master, September 11, 1992; Betacam SP (Box 7, Cassette 9)
    - Kings On The Hill, Ossie Davis Narration, Tape 1, no date; Betacam SP (Box 7, Cassette 10)
    - Kings On The Hill, Ossie Davis Narration, Tape 2, no date; Betacam SP (Box 7, Cassette 11)
    - Kings On The Hill, Ossie Davis Narration, Tape 1, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 7, Cassette 12)
    - Kings On The Hill, Ossie Davis Narration, Tape 2, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 7, Cassette 13)
    - Last Few Minutes of Ossie Narration, no date; 3/4 inch Videocassette (Box 7, Cassette 14)
    - Kings On The Hill, Mal Goode #1, February 23, 1991; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 1)
    - Kings On The Hill, Mal Goode #3, February 23, 1991; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 2)
    - Kings On The Hill, Mal Goode #4, February 23, 1991; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 3)
    - Kings On The Hill, Mal Goode #5, February 23, 1991; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 4)
    - Kings On The Hill, Mal Goode #6, February 23, 1991; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 5)
    - Kings On The Hill, Reverend Harold Tinker #5, no date; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 6)
    - Kings On The Hill, Reverend Harold Tinker #6, no date; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 7)
    - Kings On The Hill, Reverend Harold Tinker #7, no date; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 8)
    - Kings On The Hill, Reverend Harold Tinker #8, no date; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 9)
    - Kings On The Hill, Reverend Harold Tinker #9, no date; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 10)
    - Kings On The Hill, Monte Irvin #16, November 3, 1990; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 11)
    - Kings On The Hill, Monte Irvin #17, November 3, 1990; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 12)
    - Kings On The Hill, Monte Irvin #18, November 3, 1990; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 13)
    - Kings On The Hill, Monte Irvin #19, November 3, 1990; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 14)
    - Kings On The Hill, Monte Irvin #20, November 3, 1990; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 15)
    - Kings On The Hill, Monte Irvin #21, November 3, 1990; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 16)
    - Kings On The Hill, Ms. Posey #23, May 16, 1991; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 17)
    - Kings On The Hill, Ms. Posey #24, May 16, 1991; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 18)
    - Kings On The Hill, Ms. Posey #25, May 16, 1991; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 19)
    - Kings On The Hill, Ms. Posey #26, May 16, 1991; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 20)
    - Kings On The Hill Sports Cavalcade, 20:00, no date; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 21)
    - San Pedro Productions "Kings On The Hill", October 26, 1993; Mini DV Cassette (Box 11, Cassette 22)
- Photographic Material, no date; II.
  - Prints, no date
    - Pittsburgh Crawfords Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Homestead Grays Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Kansas City Monarchs Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Giants Prints, Chicago American Giants Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Newark Eagles Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Keokuk Indians Baseball Club Print, Moses Fleetwood Walker Print, no date (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Nashville Elite Giants Prints, no date (Box 14, Folder 7)